Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Team Six. Team Six.
You are cleared
to proceed. Over.
Copy that.
...European summit
will not only improve
the damaged
transatlantic relations
but solve the most
festering issues
between the U.S.
and its European allies.
Yet tension remains sky-high
as France and Germany
have repeatedly accused
United States
of intensifying
their war on terror
using secret armies
of mercenaries
to carry out various
political assassinations
in North Africa.
America has obviously
denied all this.
Over the past week,
President Lane held numerous
one-on-one meetings
with the European leaders
to offer an olive branch.
-It is time to put
the past lows behind us.
I am here to build bridges
and opportunities
for all our peoples.
The tide of conflict
and misunderstandings
must recede.
My presidency does not,
and will not meddle
in the affairs of
other nations.
America is here
to offer counsel
to its allies,
not weapons.
Vaccines, not bullets.
-Clear!
Any sign of the target?
No, sir. Not yet.
The back room is clear, sir.
Colonel, there is
something here on the table.
-How could you let him
get away? Goddamn it.
-What?
Ryder?
Ryder, is that you?
Ryder, you've gotta stop
this madness.
There's no time for theatrics.
Theatrics?
That's funny coming from you.
-Ryder, where are you?
I can talk to you.
I can come to you.
Wherever you are,
I can get there fast.
Tell me where you are.
Can you get there
faster than a bullet?
-Find me Ryder Ward!
Point all the satellites
at Valletta!
He's going after the president!
We're running out of time.
Let's go.
-Excuse me, sir.
Shouldn't you be--
-We're in the shitter here.
We have no time to waste.
Come on! Come on!
- What?
- We have a major problem.
-What did you say?
-Operative 3519 has snapped.
He's going after the president.
-Welcome to Malta. Next.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Great. How are you?
Good.
It's great to see you.
-Surprise!
-Oh, it certainly is a surprise.
How you doing, beauty?
-Good, how are you?
-I'm good.
Look at you,
how beautiful.
-Wow.
-"Wow"?
-That's all you have to say?
-How'd it happen?
-Well--
-You need me to explain
the process?
I mean, I can if you want.
I just figured
at your advanced age,
you'd know this shit already.
-At my advanced age?
- Yeah.
- Stop it.
-I appreciate you coming, man.
It means a lot.
-I always come, man. Always.
We had an agreement.
-I know. I know.
There's money to be made.
Good money.
-Yeah.
-We-can-retire kind of money.
Well, I am retired,
and there's always
money to be made
but we agreed we wouldn't work
for this son of a bitch.
- I know, but I got--
- Guys.
Come on. No business talk yet.
Let's go.
-No.
-Okay.
Blame him.
-Yeah, always.
What are you doing?
-You sure you wanna
do this, man?
You're having a baby.
-Hey, it's all good, man.
I got this.
We got this.
You gotta trust me, okay?
-Yeah, I trust you.
-You trust me?
-I trust you.
-Good.
-Are you okay with this?
-You need a woman in your life.
-I had one.
It didn't work out.
-Pity. I miss Selina.
I heard she has
her own outfit now in Rome.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, I heard that.
It's none of my business.
-You're gonna love
the new place.
It's got a gym, pool,
private beach.
We call it The Fortress.
It's like a five-star resort.
It sounds great.
-Does it have a nursery?
-Yo! Ladies!
Yeah!
-Wow. Jesus,
Mary and the Saints.
-You've really scraped
the bottom of the barrel!
-Now you know
how I fucking feel.
-Oh, yeah.
-Welcome back, brother.
- You guys are getting fat!
- Yeah.
How are you?
Good to see you, brother.
You too.
You too. Get over here.
You're all getting fat!
-Alright, he's here. Gotta go.
Ah! Boom! Boom!
-I swore I heard you say
that you quit.
-I did quit.
-No, no. I believe
his exact words were,
"You'd sooner find me dead
-than on another mission."
-Another mission.
Yeah.
-This...
is my very last mission.
-One more mission.
-Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Hey, look who made it.
-That's a great suit.
You running for governor?
-It's time for you to start
believing in something again.
I'm very sorry about
what happened in Syria.
I really am.
-I lost a lot of good men.
-It's always sad
when the shit hits the fan.
-Shit didn't hit the fan,
Colonel.
You fucked up.
We almost didn't
make it out alive.
I'm gonna do this
one more time, Colonel.
For my brother.
And then we're done.
I don't wanna see you again.
-The dead can't return...
but the living...
can be saved.
Operation Brimstone.
As always, our job
is to hunt down
those with influence
and those that abuse
their power,
and eliminate them
by any means necessary.
Our target,
Khalid Mustafa Atef.
Once a simple farmer,
he has now grown to be
one of the most powerful
warlords in Libya.
-He sounds nice.
Reliable intel tells us
Russia and China
both have a strong interest
in this region.
He needs to be stopped
before we're dragged
into a proxy war.
-Alright, boys.
Let's go hunting.
Now, as always,
you're gonna have
a specific task, each of you.
You're gonna be dropped
three clicks from the target
on the outskirts of Sirte.
Your drop-off is your pick-up.
If you're not back
by 0300 hours,
prepare for a nice long hike
back to Tunisia.
-Khalid has taken over
the Grand Hotel
that was built by Qaddafi
to house world leaders.
He's transformed
this bombed-out hotel
into his military headquarters.
-Question. Is the Jacuzzi
still working?
'Cause I might wanna
soak my balls
after this fight.
This is not
some bush league militia
you're gonna face.
Our guy has acquired
an envious arsenal.
These men are well-equipped.
You'll be facing a growing army
of professional soldiers.
Now our first task
is to isolate Khalid.
We need to cut off
his communications
with the outside world.
Forty feet underground
beneath the Grand Hall,
lies his bunker.
This is where
you will find him.
you will kill him.
Khalid is engaged in a war
on two fronts as we speak.
And most of his men
are engaged in battle.
Satellite images show us
that his bunker is protected
only by the elite
of the Sidi Omar Brigade.
Twenty men, heavily armed
rabid fanatics.
Rosebud and Femi,
you're gonna set up
on the third floor.
Guard the whole perimeter.
There are
security cameras
that are throughout
the building,
so we're gonna need to have
Hollywood set up shop
in the electrical substation
at the back of the hotel.
We need to be invisible.
-You sure this will work?
One hundred percent sure.
-Yeah, right.
-It's the only way
to get into
an air-gapped system.
We need to increase
the strain of the power supply
on the solar-metered
ultrasonic frequencies
and transport...
our information.
It's fucking genius.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Blah, blah, blah.
It's all Chinese to me.
Just make sure you get it.
-It's physics.
-Room clear.
Set.
-In the nest, over.
Hold up.
We got a guard
upstairs from you.
Hollywood, how are we doing?
Need help with those cameras.
-Sharpen the arrows,
for it's the vengeance
of the Lord.
-Hey, brother.
Can you tell him
your nice speech,
just a little bit faster?
-Father, forgive them
for they know not what they do.
All clear.
-One between you
and the target.
I need to update my equipment.
-Something feels off.
My Spidey sense is tingling.
-And here comes
the poor man's light show.
Go!
Okay, guys.
We made it. Khalid is ours.
The target is gone.
I repeat,
the target is gone.
-What the fuck is going on?
-Um...
-Oh, fuck.
-Fuck!
-It's a trap.
-They're everywhere.
Come on! Get out!
-Eyes! Eyes!
Look at me! You good?
-I'm okay.
-Alright. Breathe. Breathe. Go!
-Contact front!
We need to move!
We need to move now!
-I'm coming.
-Move! Move! Move!
-Put your guns down!
-Tell the Lord to do
what he can to save us now!
-The Lord is always with us.
-Break right!
Shit!
Eddie, stay with me, brother.
- Santa Maria...
We gotta move!
No!
-RPG!
- I was hoping you'd say that.
-Move! Faster!
-I can't!
Move! You fucking can move.
Move!
- You good?
- Oh, no. I'm bad.
- How bad?
- Real fucking bad.
-I guess you're not gonna
leave me, huh?
-You go, I go.
- Oh, fuck you.
Fuck. I'm out.
I'm sorry, brother.
-No!
-No, no, no! No.
I got you.
Look at me!
What did you do?
What the fuck did you do?
What did you do?!
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes. You're okay.
Hey, you're okay!
Fuck.
Tommy. Tommy...
-Any news yet?
-I still haven't heard anything.
Still waiting.
How's the baby?
-Good. I just...
I just have this bad feeling.
-Why don't you
run on back to bed?
I'll come get you a soon
as the bird picks 'em up, okay?
Everything's gonna be fine.
American President Lane
has just touched down
in Portugal,
making his first official stop
of "Vaccine, Not Bullets"
European tour.
All eyes on President Lane
as he breaks bread
for the first time
with Portuguese Socialist
President, Ana Nazario.
His female counterpart has,
for years, been openly critical
of U.S. foreign policy.
-Champagne, sir?
President Lane
was all smiles this morning
as he insisted
with his counterpart
that his patriotism
has a humane face.
-Hello. Shall we dance?
-Not now. Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
Thanks.
-No one's arguing
with his reputation
but given our very public stance
on international relations,
his history is toxic.
-It's just that, sir, history.
What you're getting from Hart
is experience, results.
-I'm not sure we can afford
his kind of results.
-He's taken care of
our problems without flinching.
Iraq, Libya, Chechnya.
I can keep going.
-Oh, goddamn it.
I'm trying to get the world
to fall in love
with America again.
Hart is always bad news.
And when the press
hears of this...
-They don't need
to hear anything.
I can delay the announcement
to the outside world.
Forever.
-Well, I'm not sure.
-Respectfully,
Hart is not the brand, sir.
You are. He will be strictly
behind the scenes.
-You really trust him?
-With my life.
-Feels to me like
we're inviting the bull
into the China shop.
-Look, I get it.
The world hates him,
but we need him.
We can't just sit on our behinds
and hope for the best.
Singing "Kumbaya"
won't deter our enemies.
-"Vaccines, Not Bullets"
is what we're selling.
-That's correct, sir.
That-that--
That's what we're selling,
but behind the scenes,
we need to be ready
for any eventuality.
We're hearing chatter.
Dangerous chatter.
-What do you mean?
What have you heard?
Mostly whispers because
we're flying blind.
That's why I'm pushing
"he who shall not be named"
to avoid a 9/11-level event...
on your watch.
-Sir...
Hart is merely
an insurance policy.
A heavily classified
insurance policy.
-Good,
because if the media
get wind of this,
my reputation,
everything I've built--
-It won't happen.
I won't let it.
-We'll give him a London post.
The Lair.
Just for a trial run.
-Very good, sir.
-We are at war,
ladies and gentlemen.
An undeclared war,
but a war nonetheless.
Our enemies aim
to topple the systems
that keep our very way
of life in check
and I would sooner die
than let those systems fail.
Let us begin.
Check the cameras.
-Go and give that bastard
a nice warm welcome.
-Can you tell Selina,
"Ryder's here"?
-There is no Selina here.
-I hope I didn't
mess up your night.
-Was this really necessary?
They told me...
you were dead.
Well, it's happy...
Well, happy to see you too.
-You know, to, um,
tell me you're alive...
I was busy.
-I cried for you.
Stupid me.
Cut him loose.
-So why are you here?
-Revenge.
-When isn't it?
-They're dead.
All of them.
-And the baby?
Who?
Hart.
-He's untouchable now.
Runs with the big dogs now.
-I don't want him.
I'm gonna break the system.
-You're out of your mind.
Nobody breaks the system.
So what does all this
have to do with me?
-I need a team.
I need you, Selina.
-Good luck, Ryder.
I'm sorry I missed your funeral.
I promise to attend
the next one.
-Oh...
-Are you gonna make it?
-Ha ha!
-Good job, Grandpa.
-Nice move.
-Uh-huh.
-That was close.
Excuse me, ladies.
Yeah? It's not
a good time right now.
Switch on your TV.
The video
showing a clandestine
and a controversial
operation in Libya
has recently surfaced online
to an investigative journalism
organization and claims
that this botched mission
was one of many
sanctioned by the U.S.
to prevent more trouble
in the war-torn region.
The State Department
has so far declined to comment.
-It was supposed to be buried.
Forgotten.
-Yeah. Well, apparently,
that didn't happen.
-Did you see all the bodies?
You embarrass me.
Solve it.
-Is everything okay, Dad?
-Yeah. Yeah, everything's
gonna be okay.
-Okay, guys. Dig in.
-Any progress?
- We're working on it.
-Work faster.
-This video was uploaded
somewhere in Rome.
We're using
the Pegasus technology
to cross-reference
our target's facial features
against all data retrieved.
We will find him, sir.
-Sir, I have something.
- When was that?
- Three days ago.
-Call Rome.
Yes, sir.
The target is gone!
Target is gone!
-Find him!
Okay...
-He needs a doctor.
-Oh, I don't need
a fucking doctor.
Oh, behave.
-That doesn't look too good.
No, he'll be fine.
- Yeah.
- Just get the morphine.
Jesus.
-The mess you get into.
Ryder?
-Ryder.
Stay with me.
-Get the morphine!
You alright?
- Yeah.
-I appreciate you coming, man.
-You gotta trust me.
-Eyes! Look at me!
Look at me!
I'm sorry, brother.
-No!
Ah.
Look who's finally awake.
-That's a hell of a spread
you have here.
-It's my great escape.
My sanctuary.
Away from lunatics
and prying eyes.
-Tell me you don't miss it.
-How well you know me.
So how's the wounded
soldier feeling?
- Never better.
Good.
-Hey.
Thank you.
-Don't thank me yet.
You haven't seen the bill.
Your face is all over the news.
You're in trouble.
Big trouble.
-When am I not?
I have a plan.
-You're gonna get yourself
killed... again.
- Maybe.
-You need me.
-I know.
I asked. You turned me down,
remember?
-I did.
Don't push it, Ryder.
Come, I'll give you a tour.
Hello, hello, hello!
Uncle Paulie's here!
Selina...
Always
more beautiful by the day.
-Thank you for doing this
at such short notice.
-Oh, anything for you...
and your friend.
Come, come.
I'll show you.
Now this...
is the best in the market!
Do you trust this guy?
-Oh, you have better options?
-Self-contained pen!
-It's either this or jail.
-As you can see here,
orthopedic mattress
for comfort.
We have a minibar at the back
underneath the desk
with all the whiskey
that you need.
You also have a bathroom,
but, oh, oh, oh!
No coco in the bathroom.
Only pee-pee.
Now, if you want internet,
satellite encrypted connection,
it is "Paulie's The Best,"
Wi-Fi password,
"AteMySausage123!"
And the best for last...
I deliver...
Come, come, come, come.
See, my friend. Come.
Come see.
How long?
-We'll be there in three days.
Just sit back and relax.
It'll be a piece of cake.
-Pressure mounts
on Lane Administration this week
following the videos
of clandestine operations
using illegal
Black-Ops mercenaries.
This, of course,
after very public pledges
that his administration
would be different.
-You gave me assurances.
-You know the game.
We deny everything.
-Oh, that's it?
That's all you have for me?
-Sir, if I may. I--
-No, you may not.
Be straight with me, Joshua.
Who's behind this?
-A disgruntled former employee.
Nothing to worry about.
-Well, forgive me,
I do worry.
I'm the one facing the press
on a daily basis.
You're ruining the brand.
-I'll handle the optics,
and Hart here
will clean this mess up.
Won't you, Hart?
-Mr. President, they're ready
for the group photo.
-I'll be right there.
I should fire you both.
-If you're serious
about your future,
I suggest you handle this
by any means necessary.
-There are rumors.
-What rumors?
-That he's on the island.
-What?
-He came over illegally
from Sicily.
My men are trying
to verify it now.
-Find him before more damage
is done, understood?
-Miss me, baby? Hmm.
-You're late.
-Mmm.
-Here's the rest of it.
-Brava.
It's not enough.
-It's what we agreed.
-Well, you did not tell me
that he was wanted
by the fucking CIA.
-It was none
of your fucking business.
You want to play me?
You want to play
the motherfucking king
of players?
Huh!?
-We had a deal.
-Fuck your deal!
Fuck it!
The price has tripled--
-Motherfucker!
-That's no way
to talk to a lady.
-You okay?
-Aren't I always?
Room service.
-Hey.
-I hope you're enjoying
the amenities, sir.
-It's not exactly five-star.
-Oh. Well, I'll be sure
to notify the staff.
Now...
let's get to work, shall we?
Malta is nearly
2,000 years old.
It's seen its fair share
of wars and conquerors.
Early Christians
built an extensive network
of catacombs and tunnels
to safeguard their faith
against the Romans.
The tunnels
were later extended,
covering half the island,
and later enlarged further
during World War II.
-So the Maltese
went underground again
to hide from the Germans.
-Precisely.
-And these tunnels,
they--they're active?
They're open?
-Indeed, they are.
-You're clever.
-I like to think so.
-Question is, how do we get
the target underground?
-Funny you should say that
because that's where
your genius comes in.
-Nope, not scary at all.
-If you miss...
even slightly...
-You can trust me.
-I've heard that before.
-I'm sorry.
-I know.
-I don't miss.
I know.
Obviously,
they're gonna have the president
in a dedicated vehicle, right?
-Obviously.
-I do my thing,
gonna separate the president,
put him in an ambulance.
-And if we play
our cards right,
we grab the package,
and deliver him
right to your door.
-What?
We have a major problem
on our hands.
-What did you say?
-Operative 3519 has snapped.
He's going for the president.
Go!
Go, go, go!
-Let's go! Let's go!
-Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get him in!
Come on!
-Where did that ambulance
come from?
Where did that ambulance
They're kidnapping
the president!
Stay on them!
-"Come to Malta," they said.
"An easy mission," they said.
"It will be fun."
-Stay calm, sir.
Everything is under...
control.
-What the hell are they doing?
-We have gunshots.
Repeat, we have gunshots.
-Stay on them.
-TBD.
-Where are they going?
-Fire on the target.
-They have nowhere to run.
Keep following them.
-Brace yourself!
We're coming in hot!
-They've gone underground.
-They could be anywhere.
There's hundreds of tunnels
all across this island.
We lost the president.
- You alright?
- Yep.
Fucking shit.
-You're late.
Sorry. Stopped for coffee.
-Good work, boys.
Come. Here. Come here.
Come, come, come.
Come here.
Come on. Come on.
-Okay. Let me see.
Let me see.
-I'm...
-Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
-Look at me.
-Look at me. Look at me.
-I got you.
I got you.
-We did it.
We did it.
- Yeah.
- We did it.
We did it.
-Come on.
So...
are you gonna kill me?
I don't know what you're after
but, uh, you must know
that my country
w-will not give in
to terrorists.
-All due respect, Mr. President,
your country is littered
with terrorists.
You're American.
-I am.
-So what are you?
S-some kind of traitor?
Who are you working with?
-The United States Government,
Mr. President.
At least I used to.
-Under whose command?
-Colonel Hart.
So who the hell are you?
-I'm just a man making a stand
for his country, Mr. President.
-So what do you want from me?
-A confession.
I read that Greek philosophers,
the Stoics,
were virtuous people.
Wanted to possess wisdom
and temperance,
courage, justice.
-Do you see yourself
as a good man?
-I don't know.
I hope my brother will be proud
of what we did here today.
-As politics has been rocked...
-I want to do something
that no American president
has done in the past few years.
I'm gonna take
full responsibility
and tell the truth.
As you know,
when my administration began,
I made certain promises,
promises that my leadership
would herald
a new era
of international cooperation,
harmony, and trust.
Sadly,
I failed to achieve
what I hoped to achieve
and some of the old,
unacceptable ways continued
under my administration.
I have to stand before you
to admit...
that I have fallen short
of what I hoped to achieve
for our great country.
-Mother--
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/pngus
Help other users to choose the best subtitles